// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I'm afraid ___ flying",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
      "of",
      "to",
      "with",
      "in"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Eating a lot of red meat is not good ___ you.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "at",
      "for",
      "on",
      "to"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "You're good ___ talking to big groups of people.",
    answer: "at",
    options: [
      "at",
      "in",
      "to",
      "for"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "She's angry ___ not being invited to the dinner",
    answer: "about ",
    options: [
      "about",
      "for",
      "of",
      "in"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "He wants to be involved ___ making the decision.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "About",
      "in",
      "on",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The activities will be similar ___ what we did last year.",
    answer: "to",
    options: [
      "at",
      "to",
      "with",
      "for"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "I'm a bit nervous ___ going somewhere so different.",
    answer: "about",
    options: [
     "about",
     "of",
     "to",
     "with"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "She's interested ___ buying the flat.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [
      "about",
      "in",
      "on",
      "to"
   ]
  },
  {
    numb:9 ,
    question: "I'm really proud ___ you!",
    answer: "of",
    options: [
    	"of",
      "to",
      "in",
      "with"

   ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "She's responsible ___ health and safety.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "in",
      "on",
      "for",
      "to"
   ]
  },

  /*you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: ,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },*/
];